Yo!
おっす 星奈
Sena...
Damn Meat... She has some nerve ignoring me...
肉め 私を無視するとはいい度胸だ
無視されたのは俺なんだけどな
I was the one who got ignored...
あ らめ～ き 気持ちいいの～
No!!
I-It feels so good!
ちょっと 何すんのよ 夜空 離しなさいよ
- Hey! What are you doing,
Yozora?! Let go of me!
- It's reaching my womb!
- W-What is this?!
- What are you holding my arms for?!
なんだよ
何押さえてんのよ バカ夜空
Hey! Stupid Yozora!
It's coming! I'm going to lose my mind!
きちゃいます おかしくなっちゃう
何かくる～きちゃう～
Something's coming! I-It's coming!
WANAWANA
QUIVER
Vigorously bursting with goodness
グッと Good 弾ける
You know, that's surprisingly addicting
案外なんだい ハマってんじゃん
Let's get the ball rolling
while you're idly acting shy!
人見知りしてる暇に 始めよう
Let's make friends and play, yeah!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
"Haganai"
I look cool, but I'm actually super lonely
クールに見えて 実は超寂しい
(My delusions went bye, bye, bye
Best friends are a nope, nope, nope, nope)
妄想ならバイバイバイ
親友なら いないいないいないいない
I'm not held back any, but this isn't enough
何不自由なく だけど足りない
(Is a happy life in the real world far, far, far away?
Best friends are a nope, nope, nope, nope)
リア充から遠い遠い遠い
親友なら いないいないいないいない
残念同士で 集まったら
If a group of unlucky people gathered together,
Ah... I can't picture it
Ah- 予想が出来ない 展開の 地雷を踏んだ
This situation is like stepping on a mine!
FIDGET
SOWASOWA
絶対絶対覗きたい
I totally, totally want to take a peek
I don't want to regret this 100 times
後悔100回したくないって
Totally toss aside and
shake off that boring pride
つまんない プライドなんて
捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Unfortunately, this idea popped into my mind,
and you know, it's surprisingly addicting
残念観念してみたら
案外なんだいハマってんじゃん
Let's find some as we
clash and rattle each other!
ぶつかって どぎまぎ合って 見つけよう
Let's make friends and play, yeah!
友達 作っちゃって遊んじゃって Yeah
I totally, totally want to take a peek
絶対絶対覗きたい
You! Toss aside and shake yourself off
YOU！ 捨てきっちゃって 振りきっちゃって
Yes! Well? What do you think of that?
Yes！ どーだいどーだいそこんとこ
本字幕由诸神卖萌组(kamigami.org)出品 仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
---诸神卖萌组---
日听：安少   翻译：银苹果   校对：喵儿 小草爱吃梨
时间轴：nono   后期：Maize
"There are No Flags at the Swimming Pool"
Ow!
Yes!
Jeez! What are you doing, idiot?!
もう 何すんのよ バカ
Th-That's my line!
そ それはこっちのセリフだ
In the holy club room! Have you no shame?
神聖な部室でなんと破廉恥な
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
か 勘違いしないでよね これは「聖剣のブラックスター」っていう
This is The Sacred Blackstar,
currently the most popular bishoujo game,
今一番話題の美少女ゲームで
and it's a moving, romantic fantasy adventure!
愛と感動の大冒険ファンタジーなの
ここは苦難を乗り越えて
The protagonist, Lucas,
has overcome great trials,
破壊神バルニバルを倒した主人公のルーカスが
defeated Valniball, the God of
Destruction, and in this moving scene,
ヒロインの女騎士セシリアと愛を確かめあってる感動のシーンで
he and the heroine, Cecilia the knight,
confirm their love for each other.
It's definitely not just some smutty scene!
決していかがわしいシーンじゃないんだから
Still, an eroge in the club room...
[eroge : pornographic game]
にしたって部室でエロゲーは
I-I didn't know!
し 知らなかったのよ
この前「キラスク」終わったあと面白そうなゲームを探して
After finishing Sparkling School
I was searching for an interesting game,
and when I asked for advice on the Net,
ネットで尋ねたら今一番熱いのはこれだって
I was told this was the hottest game right now.
それでクラスの男子に頼んだら
Then I asked a boy in class to get it,
喜んで持ってきたから それで
and he was more than happy to bring it, so...
You pervert!
このド変態が
Did you hear a word I just said?!
あんた今の話聞いてなかったの
黙れ 痴女 色情狂 露出狂 アバズレ
Clam it, nympho!
Jezebel!
Exhibitionist!
Hussy!
Walking public toilet!
歩く公衆便所 リアルダッチワイフ 歩く猥褻物
Real Dutch wife!
Walking obscenity!
寄るな 触るな 子供ができる
Stay away from me! Don't
touch me! You'll get me pregnant!
Why do I have to be subjected to
your abuse just for playing a game?!
なんでゲームやってただけでそこまで言われなきゃいけないのよ
Certainly, this game includes
some graphic depictions,
確かにこのゲームには過激な表現が含まれるわ
but that's only one part of it!
でもそれは一部にすぎないの
"The Brothers Karamazov"
これは重厚なテーマを持った
This is a profound tale
with heavy-hitting themes
そこら辺文学なんか目じゃないくらい奥深い物語なの
that your literature can't hold a candle to!
In other words, it's a work of art!
言わば芸術作品なのよ
You say that, when your eyes
were glued to that raunchy scene...
卑猥なシーンを食入るように見ていたくせに
Be honest and admit you're a pervert!
素直に言ってしまえ 自分は変態だと
I-I'm not! I just wanted
to be friends with Cecilia!
ち 違う 私はただセシリアと仲良くなりたかっただけ
あたしのセシリアへの気持ちはとってもピュアなものなの
My feelings for Cecilia are pure!
- Take this scene! This scene, naturally,
isn't dirty in the least, whatsoever!
- Don't show me that, pervert!
このシーンだって
全くこれっぽっちもいかがわしくなんてないの
そんなものを見せるな変態
Now that's a stretch...
それは無理があるだろう
I feel sorry for you,
こんな素晴らしい芸術を嫌らしい目でしか見られないなんて可哀相
for looking at this wonderful
piece of art through leering eyes!
In that case, Meat, try
reading that scene out loud!
だったら肉 そのシーンを声に出して読んでみろ
If it's an unobjectionable work
of art, you should be able to do so
いかがわしくない芸術作品なら 全然恥ずかしくなどないはずだ
without the slightest bit of embarrassment.
Right?
そうだろう
Of course!
勿論よ
B-But I get a little nervous
reading out loud in front of people...
で でも 人の前で文章を朗読するのはちょっと…
だったら 私も読んでやろう
In that case, I'll read, too.
Yozora?
夜空
I'll do a dramatic reading
too, but you go first.
私も朗読するから お前も読んでみせろ
Unless it's something else?
それとも何か
Perhaps that game isn't art after all...
やっばりそのゲームは芸術でもなんでもないのか
I bet the game's heroine is
nothing more than a cheap sex doll.
ゲームのヒロインも定款一万底々の安物のダッチワイフにすぎないのな
Nobody talks like that about Cecilia!
セシリアのことを悪く言ったら許さないわよ
Fine! You wanna go there, we'll go there!
いいわ そこまで言うならやってやろうじゃない
Ready? Start!
"L-Lucas, quickly... cleave my...
ル ルーカス
早く私のいけないバルニバルを
...naughty Valniball..."
With a louder voice!
もっと大きな声で
わ 私のいけないバルニバルを
"...m- my naughty Valniball...
...w- with your big, gleaming, black...
あ あなたの大きくて黒光りしている聖剣で貫いて
...sacred sword."
"You want my sacred sword that badly?
そんなにも俺の聖剣が欲しいのか
Cecilia, you really are
a randy sow, aren't you?"
セシリアは本当に淫乱な雌豚だな
い 意地悪なこと言わないで ルーカス
"D-Don't be mean, Lucas!"
"Hmph, look at your greedy expression.
ふん物欲しそうな顔をしやがって
Come on, sow. If you want this,
try asking me more politely."
ほら 雌豚
こいつが欲しければ もっと丁寧におねだりしてみろ
お お願いします ご主人様
"P-Please, Master!
Y-Your dirty-minded servant... begs you to...
あ あなたの聖剣を やららしい私の ここに挿入してくれ
...insert your sacred sword here..."
"Not 'sacred sword.' Say the proper name."
聖剣ではない 正式名称を言ってみろ
What's wrong? Go on, say it!
どうした ほら早く言ってみろ
"Lucas, I want your...
ル ルーカスの お を…
...in my hungry p-p-p..."
わ 私の嫌らしい お お を
Like I can say that, moron!
言えるかバカ
Yozora, you idiot! Moron! Scum! Drop dead!
夜空のバカ アホ カス 死ね！
I think you went overboard.
さすがにやりすぎじゃないか
By the way, I was secretly
recording Meat's recitation.
ところで今の肉の朗読をこっそり録音してあるのだが
Do you think I should put it to
good use and upload it to some site?
せっかくだし どこかのサイトにアップすべきか
Are you a devil?!
鬼か お前は
I'm kidding.
冗談だ
Oh.
なんだ
私も約束したからな 芸術作品を朗読してやるって
I promised too, didn't I?
To read aloud from a work of art...
"Upon the filthy sorrow, the
snow lightly falls again today.
「汚れちまった悲しみに、今日も小雪の降り掛かる」
Upon the filthy sorrow, even
the wind blows too hard today."
「汚れちまった悲しみに、今日も風さえ吹き過ぎる」
中原中也かよ
Nakahara Chuya, huh?
I'm home!
ただいま～
クックック ようこそ戻った 我が半身よ
I'm pleased you've returned, my other half.
I've been expecting you.
Now, offer me a sacrifice.
待ちかねたぞ さぁ 我に生贄を捧げよ
Are you hungry, Kobato?
腹減ったか 小鳩
"Kobato" is a mere alias.
小鳩とは仮の名に過ぎぬ
My name is Raysis Vi Felicity Sumeragi!
我が真名は
レイシス·ヴィ·フェリシティ·煌
A true ancestor of the great Night Tribe...
偉大なる夜の血族の真祖なり
And now, I'm thirsting for blood.
今の我は血に飢えている クックック
If you don't submit a sacrifice
quickly, disaster will befall you.
早く生贄を差し出さねば 災いが降りかかることになろう
Yeah, yeah. I'm gonna make food now.
はいはい 今作るから
It's ready!
できたぞ
Sorry for the wait.
待たせたな
クックック ご苦労
You did well.
The lifeblood of a virgin truly is special.
やはり処女の生き血は格別だ
It's just tomato juice.
トマトジュースだろ
"Out of Control!? Midnight at Takayama Zoo"
And now, some heartwarming news...
さて次はほのぼのとしたニュースです
動物園のサル山で
Eat your onions, too!
玉根もちゃんと食えよ ほら
Here.
Good.
よろしい
"Fullmetal Necromancer Eps. 1-4"
By the by, my other half...
時に我が半身よ
Recently, haven't your
offerings been on the scrawny side?
最近我への供物が貧相ではないか
Oh, yeah. I'm not able to get home
as early because I've got the club.
ああ 最近は部活があって早く帰れないからな
It can't be helped.
しかたないだろう
Which is more important, me or the club?
我と部活やらどちらが大切なのだ
部活だよ
The club.
だったらお前が作るか
If you're gonna complain,
why don't you make dinner?
Anyway, the juice...
ところでジュース じゃなくて 生き血がなくなったけん
I mean, we're out of lifeblood.
I'll buy some more tomorrow.
明日買ってくるから
Thanks...
ありがと じゃなくて えっと 大義であった
I mean, how wearisome.
About a year ago,
一年くらい前 小鳩はアニメ「鉄のネクロマンサー」にハマってしまい
Kobato got hooked on that
anime series, Fullmetal Necromancer.
Since then, she's identified herself
with a character inspired by its worldview.
それ以来アニメの世界観からインスパイアされたキャラになりきっているらしい
Dad bought this house right after I was born,
ここは俺が生まれたのをきっかけに父さんが購入した家だが
but we had to move ten
years ago because of his work,
十年前仕事の都合で引っ越して以来ずっと放置されていた
so it's been sitting empty all this time.
This spring, when we found out Dad
was going to be transferred to America,
この春 父さんがアメリカに転勤することが決まった時
it was decided that Kobato
and I would stay in Japan,
俺と小鳩は日本に残ることになり
and so we returned to
this town and our old house.
この家のある町に戻ってきたわけだ
Of course, I hardly remember
anything about living here before...
戻ってきたといっても 覚えていることなんてほとんどないんだが
小鳩 風呂沸いたぞ
Kobato, the bath's ready!
I'll get in after I watch this!
これ見たら入る
My club is important?
部活が大切か
You're not playing an eroge today, huh?
今日はエロゲーじゃないだな
The Sacred Blackstar!
「聖剣のブラックスター」よ
今日はあの性悪雌狐がないから
That malicious vixen isn't here today,
so I can play in peace and quiet.
落ち着いてゲームができるわ
She said a book she wants goes on sale today.
欲しい本の発売日なんだと
Kodaka...
小鷹ってさ その 泳げる？
Um... Can you swim?
Yeah, sorta-kinda...
まあ そこそこ
Really?
本当に？
だったらさ あたしに泳ぎ方教えてくんない？
In that case...
...will you teach me how to swim?
You can't swim?
お前 泳げないのか
My elementary school
didn't have swimming lessons.
小学校からずっと水泳の授業なんてなかったのよ
I see. Well, it'd be no trouble
teaching you, but why all of a sudden?
なるほど じゃあ教えるのは構わないけど なんで急に
そんなことも分かんないの？
You don't know that, either?
Now that I'm friends with Natsumi,
how awkward is it gonna be
夏美と友達になって一緒にプールとか海に行った時
if we go to a pool or beach
together and I can't swim?!
泳げなかったら困るじゃないの
Good grief, "Natsumi"...
お前 夏美って
So we'll go to Sea God's
Palace Land this coming Sunday, okay?
それじゃ明後日の日曜日に竜宮ランドね
Yeah. All right.
ああ 分かった
One more thing, Kodaka...
あと小鷹
Don't you dare tell that stupid
Yozora that I can't swim, got it?!
夜空のバカにはあたしが泳げないこと絶対に秘密ね
今日は肉は来ないのか
Meat's not coming today?
Yeah, she said she's going shopping.
ああ 買い物があるんだとさ
No wonder it feels so comfortable...
道理で今日は実に快適だ
Don't you dare tell that stupid
Yozora that I can't swim, got it?!
夜空のバカには絶対に秘密ね
Something on your mind?
何か用か
No. Is that the book you bought yesterday?
いや その本昨日買ったやつか
Yeah.
そうだ
Is it interesting?
面白いか
Yes.
面白い
You're late!
遅いわよ
ああ すまん
Sorry...
"Sea God's Palace Land"
Sorry to make you wait, Kodaka.
お待たせ 小鷹
What?
何？
N-Nothing. We've gotta shower first...
いや 取りあえずシャワーだな
I can get in myself.
自分で降りるわ
Okay, first, try opening your eyes underwater.
じゃまず水中で目開けてみな
Are you making fun of me?! Anyone can do that!
バカにしてんの
それくらい誰にだってできるじゃないの
How was that?
どう？
You pass.
合格 ならバタ足から始めるか
So let's go on to the flutter kick.
Too bad.
残念 もうちょっとだったのに
I almost had you.
でも泳ぐのって全然簡単じゃない
But swimming's totally easy!
Man, she's a quick study!
上達早えー
Here you go.
お待たせ
Thanks. I thought learning
how to swim would take longer.
ありがとう
思ったより早く泳げるようになったわ
これでいつ夏美が現れても大丈夫ね
Now, if Natsumi ever shows up, I'll be ready.
絶対現れないと思うが
I'm pretty sure she's not gonna show up.
にしても豪華なプール施設だよな
Anyway, this is a swanky facility...
I hear it's on the verge of bankruptcy, though.
もうすぐ潰れるっぽいけどね
Really?
そうなのか
There's hardly anyone here, right?
客が全然来てないでしょう
あと何年持つかって前にしちゃうパパに話したのよ
The last time the mayor came over,
he and Daddy were talking about
how many more years it could last.
"Daddy"...Oh, the president of the academy...
パパ…あ 学園の理事長か
そう
Right...
Come to think of it,
I haven't met the president yet.
そういや まだ理事長と会ったことなかったな
Maybe I should stop by to pay my respects...
やっばり挨拶しに行ったほうがいいかな
W-W-Why would you pay Daddy your respects?!
なんであんたがうちのパパに挨拶するのよ
You're not thinking...
まさかあんた あたしと つ 付き合ってるつもりじゃないわよね
...th-that you're going out with me, are you?!
Don't tell me that you think
this is a d-date or something?!
今日のこれがまさか デ デートとかいうものだとでも思ってるわけ？！
You've got the wrong idea!
何勘違いしてんだ
My old man and your dad are old friends,
俺の親父がお前の親父さんと昔からの友達で
so I thought I'd drop by to thank him
俺がこの学園に編入する時世話になったから
for helping out with the admissions process.
挨拶に行こうかってだけだ
Y-You should've told me that first, dummy!
そ それならそうと先に言いなさいよ バカ
I'm not responsible for your
imagination running away from you!
お前が勝手に暴走したんだろう
Kodaka, you've got some gall,
challenging me like that.
小鷹如きがこのあたしに逆らうなんて生意気
Meat...
肉…
Excuse me?!
何？
Oh! The meat in the yakisoba...
あっいや 焼き蕎麦の肉に硬くて噛みきれないやつが入ってた
One piece was so tough that
my teeth couldn't get through it.
Don't say ambiguous things!
紛らわしいこと言わないでよ
More like you're
hyper-sensitive to the word "meat"...
つーか お前しっかり肉っていうのに反応してんのな
It's that idiot! She gave
me such a weird nickname!
あのバカ！変なあだ名付けてくれちゃって
And yet, it feels like you accepted
it readily enough from the beginning...
その割には最初からあっさり受け入れてた気がするんだが
あ あだ名って初めてだったから
B-Because it was the first time
anyone's ever given me a nickname...
So I was, uh, a little h-happy...
その ちょっと 嬉しくて
嬉しい？
Happy?
D-Don't you ever tell Yozora that!
よ 夜空には絶対内緒だからね
But enough of that, Kodaka! If you're
done eating, let's get back to swimming!
っていうかほら小鷹 食べ終わったらさっさと泳ぐわよ
ああ ちょっと待ってくれ
Give me a minute.
Her first nickname...
初めてのあだ名ね
I'd consider "Meat" more
of an insult than a nickname...
肉はあだ名じゃなくて悪口だと思うけどな
Taka! Hey, Taka!
タカ おい タカ
Get away from me!
近付かないでよ
Who's this broad?!
この女
Wench!
てめぇ
あんたたちみたいなモブキャラ風情が
You think riffraff like you are in a
position to talk to me on even terms?
この私と対等に口を利いていても思ってるの
Bitch!
こら アマ
Here we go...
しょうがねえな
And what's your deal?!
つーか先からなんなんの？
こらだのアマだの ワンボターンな反応ばっか
"Broad," "bitch"...Your responses
all follow just one pattern!
Don't you think your
vocabularies need a major upgrade?!
ボキャブラリー貧困すぎじゃない？
Don't mess with us, bitch!
ざけんなよ こら
Hey, hold up!
おい 待てよ こいつ足震えじゃねぇ？
Are her legs quivering?
うわ マジだ
Totally!
The hell, she's actually scared!
なんだビビってたのかよ
W-What are you talking about?!
何勘違いしてるのよ
My legs are not quivering!
震えてるわけないでしょう
Sena!
星奈
小鷹
Kodaka!
What do you want?!
She's with me.
そいつの連れだけど
Crap. She's with a guy?
ちぇっ 男連れかよ
Should've said that from the start!
なら最初っから言えってんだよ
Wait!
待ちなさいよ よくもこの私を侮辱してくれたわね
How dare you insult me?!
Reason dictates that you get down
on your hands and knees and grovel!
這いつくばって土下座でもするのが筋ってもんでしょうが
That or die long before your time!
でなきゃ可及的速やかに死ぬか
What was that, bitch?!
だっと てめぇ
暴力はよくないだろう
Violence isn't the answer.
Frickin' let go of me!
離しやがれ てめぇ
Asshole!
Ow!!
ここは俺に免じで引いてくれないかな
Would you guys do me a favor and walk away?
S-Sure...
わ 分かった
Thanks for understanding.
分かってくれてありがとう
You okay?
大丈夫か
何なんだよ こいつは
Good work, Kodaka.
ご苦労さん小鷹
特別に足を舐めてもいいわよ
You can lick my feet as a reward, if you like.
Yeesh. I can't deal with morons
who don't know their own place.
まったく 身の程を弁えない頭の悪いやつは困るわ
頭が悪いのはお前だ バカ
You're the moron! Idiot!
W-What?!
な 何よ！
Why did you go out of
your way to provoke them?!
なんでわざわざ挑発するんだよ
Guys who hit on girls can be found everywhere!
ナンパ目的なやつなんてどこにいてもいるんもんだ
な なんなのよ小鷹
W-What's your problem, Kodaka?!
I was nice enough to compliment
you, and you're lecturing me?
せっかく私が褒めてあげたのに お説教？
That's right. I'm lecturing you!
そうだよ 説教だよ
世の中もっとタチの悪いやつだってたくさんいる
There are a lot of guys out
there much nastier than that!
This isn't the club room!
ここは部室じゃねんだぞ
I won't always be around to protect you.
いつも俺が守ってやれるわけじゃないし
Oh, shut up! I'll deal with
that when the time comes!
うっさいわね その時はその時よ
It has nothing to do with you, Kodaka!
小鷹には関係ないでしょう
It has nothing to do with me, my ass!
関係ないわけないだろう
I-It has to do with you?
か 関係なくないって
All right, my bad! From now on,
I'll be more careful, okay?
あー もう 悪かったよ
今度から気をつければいいんでしょう
O-Okay...
I'm done for today.
今日はもう帰る
That was the first time a boy my
age has seriously gotten mad at me...
同い年の男の子に本気で怒られたのは初めて
Well, here's where we part ways...
じゃ ここで
Yeah...
Th-Thank you for today.
きょ 今日はありがとうね その 色々と
For everything...
Let's go again!
また行きましょう 波のプールとか遊びたいし
I wanna play in the wave pool next time.
S-Sure...
She's in a good mood again?
機嫌 直ったのか
You need to be taken down a peg, boy!
てめぇ生意気だぞ
You got somethin' to say to that?!
とっとと言ってみろ
Come to think of it, this hair of mine
used to get me in a lot of scrapes...
そういや この髪のせいか昔はよく絡まれたな
あんちゃん
An-chan!
Kobato! What's wrong?!
小鳩 どうしたんだ
The bath! The bath water turned cold!
お風呂が お風呂が水になっちょるばい
え マジで？
Really?!
- It's a conspiracy! I'm not
gonna take a bath ever again!
- Okay, just put something on.
陰謀じゃ
もう一生風呂に入れないんじゃ
いいから 何か着ろ
Stop bullying weak kids!
弱い者虐めは止めろ
なんだてめぇ
What's it to you?!
な なにすんだよ
W-What was that for?! I was trying to help you!
助けてやろうとしたのに
I'm not weak!
俺は 弱い者じゃない！
上等だこの野郎
Then bring it on!
Don't ignore me!
無視すんなよ こいつ！
You...
Get 'em!
やっちまえ！
Jerk!
この野郎
Give it up!
覚悟しろ
Little brat!
この野郎
From then on, he and I were fast friends...
その時から俺はあいつと遊ぶようになった
Taka...
タカ
My mom once said...
俺の母さんが前に言ってた
"When you're in first grade, it doesn't
matter if you can't make 100 friends.
一年生になったら友達百人できなくてもいいから
Instead, make real friends who are
as important to you as 100 of them.
百人分大切にできるような
本当の友達に作りなさいって
It doesn't matter if you only have one,
たっだ一人だけでも
大切に思える本当の友達がいれば
as long as it's a real
friend that you care about."
I like the way your mom thinks.
いいな お前の母さん
Yeah...
In that case, I'll value
you as much as 100 friends...
だったら俺は  のことを百人分大切に大切するよ
Even if the whole world becomes
your enemy, I'll always be your friend.
世界が敵になっても
俺だけはお前の友達でいる
D-Don't say such embarrassing things!
は 恥ずかしいこと言ってんじゃねえよ
You started it!
そっちが先に言い出したんだろう
W-Well, yeah, but...
ま まあ そうだけどな
いつの間にか寝ちまった
Must've fallen asleep...
"Make real friends who are as
important to you as 100 of them..."
百人分大切にできる本当の友達を作りなさいっか
K-Kodaka...
こ 小鷹 覚え…
You remem...
Is something wrong?
どうかしたのか
N-Nothing!
な なんでもない
いきなり小鷹が喋るから驚いただけだ
I was just surprised when you
started muttering all of a sudden!
Oh. Sorry...
そうか 悪かったよ
By the way, where's Sena?
ところで星奈は？
Meat already went home.
肉はもう帰った
What about you, Yozora?
夜空は？
I-I was reading my book, so...
わ 私は本を読んでいたから
Well, I'm gonna go home, too.
そんじゃ俺も帰るわ
I wonder what that kid is doing now?
あいつは今どうしているだろうか
Does he still live in this town?
今もこの街に住んでいるのだろうか
What did I call him then again?
あの時俺はあいつのことをなんで呼んだんだっけ
Oh, well, it was a long time ago.
どうせ昔のことだ
I'm sure he doesn't remember
what happened ten years ago, either.
あいつだって十年前のことなんて覚えてないだろう
Is there even such a thing as friends...
一生お互いを大切に思える友達なんて
...who treasure each other forever?
本当に有りうるのだろうか
あー 脳內 想像理想の 現実逃避
Ah, my mind is escaping
reality as ideally as imaginable
今更どっちだっていっけど 友達作り
Not that it really matters
now if I... make friends
一人寂しい奴だと蔑む 視線が気になる
Those eyes that belittle me saying,
"You're a lonesome person on your own," bug me
で 上っ面だけ集まったら
So, while I was thinking that it'd be cool...
それでいいと 思っているうちに
...if only a superficial group gathered up,
あれよあれよと登場 揃って 破天荒な奴らに
They show up, one here,
one there, and gather together
The unique characters
Throw me off balance
マイペース 乱されてゆく 頭くる！特に憎っくき肉
It ticks me off! Especially that mean meat!
My chest is secretly filled with
apprehension and I feel a bit indecisive
私の胸秘かに焦って 優柔不斷気味で
I can't tell you what's in my heart
My heart 伝えられない 殘念なのは 私なのか
Am I the one disappointed by that?
もやもやを かきわけ Today！
Plow through the fog today!
置き去りにされた 乙女心 あの日から悔やんでいる
Ever since the day I got left behind,
my maiden heart has been filled with regret
早く見つけ出して 迷子のココロ
Hurry and find it...my lost heart
ねね夜空 あんた泳げる？
Hey, Yozora, can you swim?
I can swim. But I have no
intention of swimming with you.
泳げる だが貴様と一緒に泳ぐつもりは毛頭ない
Shoot. Boring!
ちぇ つまんない
あんたが泳げなくてあたしに土下座するなら
If you couldn't swim,
I was going to offer to teach you
if you got down on your
hands and knees and begged.
泳ぎ教えてあげてもいいかなって思ったのにな
あーあ せっかく泳げるようになったし
Now that I know how to swim,
I wish there was someone I could teach...
誰か教える相手いないかなー
Now that you know how to swim?
泳げるようになった お前 誰かに教わたのか
Did someone teach you?
何でもないから何でもない
Never mind! Forget I said anything!
Next time: "Underclassmen Don't Hold Back."
次回 後輩達は遠慮がない
"Next time: Underclassmen Don't Hold Back"
Who's the underclassman?
後輩ってなによ？まさか隣人部に部員が増えるわけ？
You mean the Neighbors Club
is getting a new member?
Don't ask me!
私に聞くな